const STORE = [
   {
       question: 'Which macronutrient below provides 7 calories per gram?',
       answers: [
           'Protein',
           'Lipids',
           'Carbohydrates',
           'Alcohol'
       ],
       correctAnswer: 'Alcohol'
   }, 
   {
        question: 'Which of the following foods contains the most Vitamin C?',
        answers: [
        '1 medium orange',
        '1/2 C chili peppers',
        '1 C strawberries',
        '1 C kale'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1/2 C chili peppers'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which macronutrient is considered the preferred energy source of brain tissue?',
        answers: [
        'Protein',
        'Lipids',
        'Carbohydrates',
        'Alcohol'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Carbohydrates'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which word belows corresponds to this definition: the energy needed to raise the temperature of 1 gram of water through 1 °C?',
        answers: [
        'Calorie',
        'Creation of fatty tissues',
        'Cholesterol',
        'Hydrolysis'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Calorie'
    },
    {
        question: 'A primary use of dietary cholesterol within the body includes:',
        answers: [
        'Synthesis of serum cholesterol',
        'Trans fat',
        'Integral part of sex hormone production',
        'A substrate for glycolysis'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Integral part of sex hormone production'
    },     
    {
        question: 'When the concept of vitamins first arose they were believed to be:',
        answers: [
        'Amines',
        'Amino acids',
        'Amide groups',
        'Aldehydes'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Amines'
    }, 
    {
        question: 'The integral difference between unsaturated and saturated fats is:',
        answers: [
        'The number of carbons in the chain',
        'The presence of a carbon-carbon double bond',
        'The carboxyl group',
        'One is hydrophilic the other hydrophobic'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'The presence of a carbon-carbon double bond'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which macronutrient below is involved with antibody production?',
        answers: [
        'Protein',
        'Lipids',
        'Carbohydrates',
        'Alcohol'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Protein'
    },
    {
        question: 'How many amino acids are essential to acquire in one’s diet?',
        answers: [
        'All of them',
        '146',
        '9',
        '21'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '9'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which macronutrient below assists in the transport and solubility of Vitamin E?',
        answers: [
        'Protein',
        'Lipids',
        'Carbohydrates',
        'Alcohol'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lipids'
    },       
];